(Howard:)You had to be taught
not to burn down the forest?
(Penny:)If you guys were hungry, why didn't
you order at the restaurant?
(Bernadette:)We did.
You never brought it.
(Penny:)Oh, that's right.
(Penny:)Nachos and a turkey club.
(Amy:)Not even close.
(Penny:)Well, I was too busy
standing up for my friend
(Penny:)to worry about your...
(Penny:)I want to say salmon.
(Amy:)You want to say sorry.
(Raj:)So, how are you gonna
tell Raj abut what you did?
What do you mean "how"?
What's the big deal?
(Amy:)You told Lucy he was a pathetic mess.
(Bernadette:)Then you made her cry and leave.
(Penny:)Okay, you guys are overreacting.
(Penny:)Raj is gonna appreciate
how had his back.
What is wrong with you, Penny?!
(Raj:)You ruined any chance I had
of getting back with Lucy!